Guide to the Lewis Perry Curtis Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Early Curtis Papers, 1762-1814; Series IV; 8.2 linear feet (20 boxes)
  - Business Papers
    - Miscellaneous and unknown, 1816-1869, undated (Box 40, Folder 1079)
  - Business Papers: Oversize
    - American Land Company: deeds, 1836-1848 (Box 41, Folder 1080)
    - Beers, Andrew: deeds, 1793-1811 (Box 41, Folder 1081)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: appointment, 1803 (Box 41, Folder 1082)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: deeds, 1836-1845 (Box 41, Folder 1083)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: estate, 1864-1865 (Box 41, Folder 1084)
    - Booraem & Co. (Texas lands): papers, 1834-1891, undated (Box 41, Folder 1085)
    - Curtis and Jones: deed, 1809 (Box 41, Folder 1086)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: Columbia College certificates, 1852-1855 (Box 41, Folder 1087)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: diplomas, 1855-1863 (Box 41, Folder 1088)
    - Curtis, Lewis: estate, 1883 (Box 41, Folder 1089)
    - Curtis, Lewis: 4 Bowling Green, 1830-1863, undated (Box 41, Folder 1090)
    - Curtis, Lewis: New York lands, 1836, 1838 (Box 41, Folder 1091)
    - Curtis, Lewis: picture of cemetery, undated (Box 41, Folder 1092)
    - 50th and 51st Streets, 1838-1852, undated (Box 41, Folder 1093)
    - Flatbush and Jamaica lands, 1836-1850 (Box 41, Folder 1094)
    - Giles, Lewis C.: accounts, 1914 (Box 41, Folder 1095)
    - Gillespie County News, 1881-1882 (Box 41, Folder 1096)
    - Indian Reservation Trust lands, 1840-1851 (Box 41, Folder 1097)
    - Jamaica, Long Island lands, 1837-1882 (Box 41, Folder 1098-1099)
    - L. & B. Curtis & Co., 1834-1868 (Box 41, Folder 1100)
    - Maps and broadsides, undated (Box 41, Folder 1101)
    - New York and Mississippi Land Co., [1834] (Box 41, Folder 1102)
    - Sherwood, Samuel and Michigan lands, 1840, 1852 (Box 41, Folder 1103)
    - Tucumbia, Cortlandt, and Decatur Railroad Co. (Alabama), 1835 (Box 41, Folder 1104)
    - Vyse, William, 1836 (Box 41, Folder 1105)
    - Business records (Box 42)
    - Business records (Box 43)
    - Business records (Box 44)
    - Business records (Box 45)
- Additional Material, Circa 1739-1765; Accession 1997-M-063
  - Photostatic copies of autograph letters of Laurence Sterne; miscellaneous family letters; and the "Continuation of the Bramine's Journal" [these photostatic copies were used by Lewis Perry Curtis in his book, Letters of Laurence Stern, and are marked with the numbers which correspond to those in the printed volume (Box 1)